Peter Wexler papers 1965 - ongoing
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Papers., Series:I
  - BSO Lighting. RFP Proposal 3 of 3. 1996 (Box 109)
  - BSO Lighting. RFP Proposal 2 of 3. 1996 (Box 109)
  - BSO Lighting. RFP Proposal 1 of 3. 1996 (Box 109)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. 1996 (Box 109)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Research Concert Lighting 3 of 3. 1996 (Box 109)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Research Concert Lighting 2 of 3. 1996 (Box 109)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Research Concert Lighting 1 of 3. 1996 (Box 109)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Lighting Contracts. 1996 (Box 109)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Lighting Plan. 1996 (Box 109)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Lighting Meeting Agenda. 1996 (Box 109)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Lighting Memorandum. 1996 (Box 109)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Lighting Transmittals. 1996 (Box 109)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Lighting Business. 1996 (Box 109)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. 1997 (Box 109)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Concert Lighting Vari-Lite. 1997 (Box 109)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Lighting Contracts 1997 (Box 109)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. 1998 (Box 109)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Lighting Vari-Lite Manual. 1998 (Box 109)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Lighting Obsession Complete System Manual. 1998 (Box 109)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Lighting Barbizon Complete System manual. 1998 (Box 109)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. 1997 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Rigging Schedules. 1997 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. 1998 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Rigging Preliminary Manual Mat’l 1 of 2. 1998 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Rigging Preliminary Manual Mat’l 2 of 2. 1998 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Rigging End Game- Model Photographs. 1998 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Rigging End Game- Fin 2nd, 3rd, Recon, Roughs 1998 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Rigging End Game GBH Beam Deflection. 1998 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Rigging End Game Labor. 1998 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Rigging End Game Variation Demonstration. 1998 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Rigging End Game Manuals 4 of 4. 1998 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Rigging End Game Manuals 3 of 4. 1998 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Rigging End Game Manuals 2 of 4. 1998 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Rigging End Game Manuals 1 of 4. 1998 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Rigging End Game Manual Drawings. 1998 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Production Manager’s Daily Log. 1998 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Summary of Systems Update Plan of 3-25-98. 1998 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. 1996 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Budget. 1996 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. 1997 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Budget Drafts 3 of 3. 1997 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Budget Drafts 2 of 3. 1997 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Budget Drafts 1 of 3. 1997 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. 1998 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Budget Tracking 1 of 6. 1998 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Budget Tracking 2 of 6. 1998 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Budget Tracking 3 of 6. 1998 (Box 110)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. 1998 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Budget Tracking 4 of 6. 1998 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Budget Tracking 5 of 6. 1998 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Budget Tracking 6 of 6. 1998 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. 1996 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Computer Disks. 1996 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Press and Publicity. 1996 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. 1997 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Press and Publicity - Opening Night Program 1997 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Reviews and Articles. 1997 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. 1996 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Test of Equipment 9-21-96. 1996 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. 1997 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Anna Beha. 1997 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Asbestos. 1997 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. 1996 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Computer Aided Design. 1996 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Print Samples. 1996 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Pictures. 1997 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. 1996 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Consultants. 1996 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Memorandum. 1996 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Contract. 1996 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Business. 1996 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Schedules. 1996 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Meeting Notes. 1996 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Transmittals. 1996 (Box 111)
  - BSO Plan Implementation. Contact Sheet. 1996 (Box 111)
  - American Anthem. 1985 (Box 112)
  - American Anthem. Press and Publicity 1 of 11. 1985 (Box 112)
  - American Anthem. Press and Publicity 2 of 11. 1985 (Box 112)
  - American Anthem. Press and Publicity 3 of 11. 1985 (Box 112)
  - American Anthem. Press and Publicity 4 of 11. 1985 (Box 112)
  - American Anthem. Press and Publicity 5 of 11. 1985 (Box 112)
  - American Anthem. Press and Publicity 6 of 11. 1985 (Box 112)
  - American Anthem. Press and Publicity 7 of 11. 1985 (Box 112)
  - American Anthem. Press and Publicity 8 of 11. 1985 (Box 112)
  - American Anthem. Press and Publicity 9 of 11. 1985 (Box 112)
  - American Anthem. Press and Publicity 10 of 11. 1985 (Box 112)
  - American Anthem. Press and Publicity 11 of 11. 1985 (Box 112)
  - NAVY. 1987 (Box 112)
  - NAVY. Story Board 1 of 2. 1987 (Box 112)
  - NAVY. Story Board 2 of 2. 1987 (Box 112)
  - NAVY. Working Story Board. 1987 (Box 112)
  - NAVY. Script. 1987 (Box 112)
  - Lifetime Medical II. Photos. 1989 (Box 112)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. 1985 (Box 112)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Meyerson Symph. Ctr. Soundtrack 1 of 9. 1985 (Box 112)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Meyerson Symph. Ctr. Soundtrack 2 of 9. 1985 (Box 112)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Meyerson Symph. Ctr. Soundtrack 3 of 9. 1985 (Box 112)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Meyerson Symph. Ctr. Soundtrack 4 of 9. 1985 (Box 112)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. 1985 (Box 113)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Meyerson Symph. Ctr. Story Board. 1985 (Box 113)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Meyerson Symph. Ctr. Rough Story Boards 4 of 4. 1985 (Box 113)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Meyerson Symph. Ctr. Rough Story Boards 3 of 4. 1985 (Box 113)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Meyerson Symph. Ctr. Rough Story Boards 2 of 4. 1985 (Box 113)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Meyerson Symph. Ctr. Rough Story Boards 1 of 4. 1985 (Box 113)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Meyerson Symph. Ctr. Notes. 1985 (Box 113)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Meyerson Symph. Ctr. Slides 2 of 2. 1985 (Box 113)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Meyerson Symph. Ctr. Slides 1 of 2. 1985 (Box 113)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Meyerson Symph. Ctr. Soundtrack 9 of 9. 1985 (Box 113)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Meyerson Symph. Ctr. Soundtrack 8 of 9. 1985 (Box 113)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Meyerson Symph. Ctr. Soundtrack 7 of 9. 1985 (Box 113)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Meyerson Symph. Ctr. Soundtrack 6 of 9. 1985 (Box 113)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Meyerson Symph. Ctr. Soundtrack 5 of 9. 1985 (Box 113)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Meyerson Symph Ctr. Slide Making Graphics 3 of 3. 1985 (Box 113)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Meyerson Symph Ctr. Slide Making Graphics 2 of 3. 1985 (Box 113)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Meyerson Symph Ctr. Slide Making Graphics 1 of 3. 1985 (Box 113)
  - Studio. Sterns Directory 2001. 1999 (Box 114)
  - Florida 2012. 2000 (Box 114)
  - Florida 2012. Contact Sheet. 2000 (Box 114)
  - Florida 2012. Transmittals/Memos/Correspondence. 2000 (Box 114)
  - Florida 2012. Business. 2000 (Box 114)
  - Florida 2012. Research. 2000 (Box 114)
  - Florida 2012. Art. 2000 (Box 114)
  - Florida Holocaust Museum. 2000 (Box 114)
  - Florida Holocaust Museum. Contact Sheet. 2000 (Box 114)
  - Florida Holocaust Museum. Research. 2000 (Box 114)
  - Florida Holocaust Museum. Book: The Secret War Against the Jews. By Mark Aarons and John Loftus. 2000 (Box 114)
  - High Altitude. 2000 (Box 114)
  - High Altitude. Transmittals/Memos/Correspondence. 2000 (Box 114)
  - High Altitude. Creative Realities. 2000 (Box 114)
  - High Altitude. Business. 2000 (Box 114)
  - High Altitude. Contract. 2000 (Box 114)
  - High Altitude. Schedules. 2000 (Box 114)
  - High Altitude. Research. 2000 (Box 114)
  - High Altitude. Photography-Slides. 2000 (Box 114)
  - High Altitude. Meeting Notes. 2000 (Box 114)
  - High Altitude. Ali’s Mother. 2000 (Box 114)
  - High Altitude. Lighting Vendors Catalogues. 2000 (Box 114)
  - Evolutia. 2000 (Box 114)
  - Evolutia. General. 2000 (Box 114)
  - Evolutia. Transmittals/Memos/Correspondence. 2000 (Box 114)
  - Evolutia. Promotion Materials. 2000 (Box 114)
  - Reliance Industries. 2001 (Box 114)
  - Reliance Industries. Contract. 2001 (Box 114)
  - Reliance Industries. Visa Health. 2001 (Box 114)
  - Reliance Industries. Budget. 2001 (Box 114)
  - Reliance Industries. Business. 2001 (Box 114)
  - BSO - Plans Implementation. 2000 (Box 115)
  - BSO - Plans Implementation. End Game- Index of All BSO Files. 2000 (Box 115)
  - BSO - Plans Implementation. Rigging- End Game General. 2000 (Box 115)
  - BSO - Plans Implementation. Rigging- End Game Backup Letters, Notes. 2000 (Box 115)
  - BSO - Plans Implementation. End Game Photos Hall Before Renovation. 2000 (Box 115)
  - BSO - Plans Implementation. End Game Photos and Negatives Christmas Pops. 2000 (Box 115)
  - BSO - Plans Implementation. Rigging- End Game Backup Contracts. 2000 (Box 115)
  - BSO - Plans Implementation. Rigging- End Game Backup Financials. 2000 (Box 115)
  - BSO - Plans Implementation. Rigging- End Game Backup Plan. 2000 (Box 115)
  - BSO - Plans Implementation. 1999 (Box 115)
  - BSO - Plans Implementation. Rigging- End Game Manual 1 of 2. 1999 (Box 115)
  - BSO - Plans Implementation. Rigging- End Game Manual 2 of 2. 1999 (Box 115)
  - BSO - Plans Implementation. Rigging- End Game Steve Walker Sup. 1999 (Box 115)
  - BSO - Plans Implementation. Rigging- End Game Clancy Drawings. 1999 (Box 115)
  - BSO - Plans Implementation. Photographs of Model. 1999 (Box 115)
  - BSO - Plans Implementation. Rigging- End Game Punch List, Phone Notes, Transmittals. 1999 (Box 115)
  - American History Workshop, NURFC. Prototype Document Draft. 1999 (Box 115)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Consulting. 1998-2000 (Box 116)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Consulting. ID Research. 1998-2000 (Box 116)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Consulting. ID Exterior Name Placement. 1998-2000 (Box 116)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Consulting. ID Computer Renderings. 1998-2000 (Box 116)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Consulting. Nextstage Promotional Videos. 1998-2000 (Box 116)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Consulting. PWI Model Photos. 1998-2000 (Box 116)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Consulting. Architect’s Model Photos. 1998-2000 (Box 116)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Consulting. General Research. 1998-2000 (Box 116)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Consulting. Las Vegas 12/00- ‘Twas Workshop. 1998-2000 (Box 116)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Consulting. Sound. 1998-2000 (Box 116)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Consulting. P.R.-Marketing. 1998-2000 (Box 116)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Consulting. Contract. 1998-2000 (Box 116)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Consulting. Meeting Notes. 1998-2000 (Box 116)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Consulting. Memos/Transmittals/ Correspondences 2 of 2. 1998-2000 (Box 116)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Consulting. Memos/Transmittals/Correspondences 1 of 2. 1998-2000 (Box 116)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. 1999-2000 (Box 116)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Alternative Projects. 1999-2000 (Box 116)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Alternative Themes- Norman Rockwell. 1999-2000 (Box 116)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Other Research Books. 1999-2000 (Box 116)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Research. 1999-2000 (Box 116)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Puppetry Research- Hensen Int’l Puppet Festival. 1999-2000 (Box 116)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Research Book II. 1999-2000 (Box 116)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Research Book 1. 1999-2000 (Box 116)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. 2000 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Pinocchio Storybooks (Engl. and Ital). 2000 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Selected Photographs 1 of 2. 2000 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Costume Sketches- Originals. 2000 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Photographs of Model. 2000 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. DVC Information. 2000 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. DVC Tapes. 2000 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. DVC Charts. 2000 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Music-Notes. 2000 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Music- Selects Chart. 2000 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Scripts 4 of 4. 2000 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Scripts 3 of 4. 2000 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Scripts 2 of 4. 2000 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Scripts 1 of 4. 2000 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. End of Phase One Document Package 2 of 2. 2000 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. End of Phase One Document Package 1 of 2. 2000 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Other Venues- Forth Worth Ballet. 2000 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Other Venues- San Francisco Ballet. 2000 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Other Venues- Pittsburgh Ballet. 2000 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Other Venues- Center Theatre Group. 2000 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Continuing Script Development. 2001 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Update and Story Development. 1/1/2001. 2001 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Continuing Script Development. 2002 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Continuing Script Development. Rough Submissions Video Images 01/01/02. 6 of 6. 2002 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Continuing Script Development. Rough Submissions Music Cut List 01/01/02. 5 of 6. 2002 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Continuing Script Development. Rough Submissions Ballet Version 01/01/02. 4 of 6. 2002 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Continuing Script Development. Rough Submissions Workshop Version 01/01/02. 3 of 6. 2002 (Box 117)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Continuing Script Development. 2002 (Box 118)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Continuing Script Development. Rough Submissions Pin Magic 01/01/02. 2 of 6. 2002 (Box 118)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Continuing Script Development. Rough Submissions Cover Letters 01/01/02. 1 of 6. 2002 (Box 118)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Continuing Script Development. Music Cuts- Preliminary Selections. 2002 (Box 118)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Continuing Script Development. Music Sources 3 of 3. 2002 (Box 118)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Continuing Script Development. Music Sources 2 of 3. 2002 (Box 118)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Continuing Script Development. Music Sources 1 of 3. 2002 (Box 118)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Continuing Script Development. Video- DVD Model. 2002 (Box 118)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Continuing Script Development. Video Images (Old from 3/1/00) 2002 (Box 118)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Continuing Script Development. Video – Current. 2002 (Box 118)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Continuing Script Development. Pictures and Sketchbook. 2002 (Box 118)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Continuing Script Development. Submissions 1/1/02. 2002 (Box 118)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Continuing Script Development. Submissions 4/2/02. 2002 (Box 118)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Continuing Script Development. Current Hand Out. 2002 (Box 118)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Continuing Script Development. Research. 2002 (Box 118)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. 1999 (Box 118)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Meeting Notes. 1999 (Box 118)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Budget. 1999 (Box 118)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Business. 1999 (Box 118)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. 2002 (Box 118)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Bankruptcy. 2002 (Box 118)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. 1999 (Box 118)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Contract. 1999 (Box 118)
  - Nextstage Ent.- Pinocchio. Laurie Shulman. 1999 (Box 118)
  - Studio. 1999 (Box 118)
  - Studio. Memos/Transmittals. 1999 (Box 118)
  - Who's Who in America. 1999 (Box 118)
  - Studio. 1997-1999 (Box 118)
  - Studio. Full Computer Back-Ups. 1997-1999 (Box 118)
  - The Florida Orchestra. 2000 (Box 118)
  - The Florida Orchestra. Meeting Notes. 2000 (Box 118)
  - The Florida Orchestra. Research. 2000 (Box 118)
  - The Florida Orchestra. Schedules. 2000 (Box 118)
  - The Florida Orchestra. Contract. 2000 (Box 118)
  - The Florida Orchestra. Transmittals/Memos/Correspondence. 2000 (Box 118)
  - Lincoln Center. General. 2000 (Box 119)
  - Studio. 2000 (Box 119)
  - Studio. ABC News Model Graphics. 2000 (Box 119)
  - Studio. Judaica Current. 2000 (Box 119)
  - Studio. “There’s a Ferry in MY Pool.” 2000 (Box 119)
  - Studio. X-mas Cards. 2000 (Box 119)
  - Studio. Full Computer Back-Ups. 2000 (Box 119)
  - Studio. Memos/Transmittals. 2000 (Box 119)
  - Boston Symphony Pops. Current. 2000 (Box 119)
  - Centre Theatre Group. General. 2000 (Box 119)
  - Look of Music Publications. (2 parts). 1989 (Box 119)
  - Centre Theatre Group. Current-General. 2001 (Box 119)
  - Theatre Junction. 2001 (Box 119)
  - Studio. 2001 (Box 119)
  - Studio. Lincoln Center General. 2001 (Box 119)
  - Studio. World Trade Center Symbol. 2001 (Box 119)
  - ROSPO- Gianpaolo Belli. 2001 (Box 119)
  - Swimming Pool. 2001 (Box 119)
  - Studio. 2001 (Box 119)
  - Studio. Christmas Cards. 2001 (Box 119)
  - Studio. Transmittals/Memos/Correspondence. 2001 (Box 119)
  - Jaffe Midland. 2001 (Box 119)
  - Jaffe Midland. Photos 3 of 3. 2001 (Box 119)
  - Jaffe Midland. Photos 2 of 3. 2001 (Box 119)
  - Jaffe Midland. Photos 1 of 3. 2001 (Box 119)
  - Jaffe Midland. Research. 2001 (Box 119)
  - Jaffe Midland. Speakers. 2001 (Box 119)
  - Jaffe Midland. Lighting Disks. 2001 (Box 119)
  - Jaffe Midland. Lighting Early Plots. 2001 (Box 119)
  - Jaffe Midland. Lighting Equipment. 2001 (Box 119)
  - Jaffe Midland. Lighting General. 2001 (Box 119)
  - Jaffe Midland. 2001 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Shell and Rigging Proposals Back-Up. 2001 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Shell and Rigging Proposals. 2001 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Shell and Rigging RFP. 2001 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Press and Public Relations. 2001 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Phase 1 Submissions. 2001 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Contact List. 2001 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. AutoCAD CDs. 2001 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Meeting Notes. 2001 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Notes. 2001 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Budget. 2001 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Contract. 2001 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Business. 2001 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Schedules. 2001 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Transmittals/Memos/Correspondence 1 of 2. 2001 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Transmittals/Memos/Correspondence 2 of 2. 2001 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. 2002 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Research Photos 4 of 4. 2002 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Research Photos 3 of 4. 2002 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Research Photos 2 of 4. 2002 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Research Photos 1 of 4. 2002 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Fabric Samples 2- From Manufacturer As Built. 2002 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Fabric Samples 1- From Us. 2002 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Research- General. 2002 (Box 120)
  - Christmas Carol. 2002 (Box 120)
  - DOW Sculpture. 2002 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. 2002 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Rug. 2002 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Back wall and Doors. 2002 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Auditorium Handicap Rails. 2002 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Ceiling. 2002 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Seating. 2002 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Orchestra Pit. 2002 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Business. 2002 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Stack and Secretarial Chair Research 3 of 3. 2002 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. Stack and Secretarial Chair Research 2 of 3. 2002 (Box 120)
  - Jaffe Midland. 2002 (Box 121)
  - Jaffe Midland. Stack and Secretarial Chair Research 1 of 3. 2002 (Box 121)
  - Jaffe Midland. Research. 2002 (Box 121)
  - Jaffe Midland. Press and Public Relations. 2002 (Box 121)
  - Jaffe Midland. Budget. 2002 (Box 121)
  - Jaffe Midland. Contract. 2002 (Box 121)
  - Jaffe Midland. Transmittals/Memos/Correspondence. 2002 (Box 121)
  - Jaffe Midland. Peter. 2002 (Box 121)
  - INGE Festival. 2002 (Box 121)
  - INGE Festival. Kander and Ebb Tribute. 2002 (Box 121)
  - Jaffe Midland. 2002 (Box 121)
  - Jaffe Midland. Contract. 2002 (Box 121)
  - Jaffe Midland. 2003-2004 (Box 121)
  - Jaffe Midland. Consultants. 2003-2004 (Box 121)
  - Jaffe Midland. Contact Sheet. 2003-2004 (Box 121)
  - Jaffe Midland. Business. 2003-2004 (Box 121)
  - Jaffe Midland. Budget. 2003-2004 (Box 121)
  - Jaffe Midland. Transmittals/Memos/Correspondence. 2003-2004 (Box 121)
  - Jaffe Midland. Peter. 2003-2004 (Box 121)
  - Jaffe Midland. Press and Public Relations. 2003-2004 (Box 121)
  - Jaffe Midland. 2003 (Box 121)
  - Jaffe Midland. Rogue’s Gallery. 2003 (Box 121)
  - Jaffe Midland. Video Tape. 2003 (Box 121)
  - Detroit Symphony. 2002 (Box 121)
  - Detroit Symphony. Final Report 2 of 2. 2002 (Box 121)
  - Detroit Symphony. Final Report 1 of 2. 2002 (Box 121)
  - Detroit Symphony. Report- Phase 1. 2002 (Box 121)
  - Detroit Symphony. Reports. 2002 (Box 121)
  - Detroit Symphony. Request for Information. 2002 (Box 121)
  - Detroit Symphony. Research. 2002 (Box 121)
  - Detroit Symphony. Research Photos 4 of 4. 2002 (Box 121)
  - Detroit Symphony. Conceptual Repot Model Shots. 2002 (Box 121)
  - Detroit Symphony. 2002 (Box 122)
  - Detroit Symphony. Research Photos 3 of 3. 2002 (Box 122)
  - Detroit Symphony. Research Photos 2 of 3. 2002 (Box 122)
  - Detroit Symphony. Research Photos 1 of 3. 2002 (Box 122)
  - Detroit Symphony. Research- Selected Photos and Drawings. 2002 (Box 122)
  - Detroit Symphony. Organ. 2002 (Box 122)
  - Detroit Symphony. Theatre Consultant Specifications. 2002 (Box 122)
  - Detroit Symphony. Press and Public Relations. 2002 (Box 122)
  - Detroit Symphony. Business. 2002 (Box 122)
  - Detroit Symphony. Contract. 2002 (Box 122)
  - Detroit Symphony. Budget. 2002 (Box 122)
  - Detroit Symphony. Meeting Notes. 2002 (Box 122)
  - Detroit Symphony. Transmittals/Memos/Correspondence. 2002 (Box 122)
  - Detroit Symphony. Peter. 2002 (Box 122)
  - Detroit Symphony. ARTEC. 2002 (Box 122)
  - US Equities. General. 2002 (Box 122)
  - Studio. Christmas Cards. 2002 (Box 122)
  - Who’s Who in America. General. 2002 (Box 122)
  - Studio. Transmittals/Memos/Correspondence. 2002 (Box 122)
  - Music EXPO. 2003 (Box 122)
  - Music EXPO. Reports. 2003 (Box 122)
  - Music EXPO. Press and Public Relations. 2003 (Box 122)
  - Music EXPO. Contract. 2003 (Box 122)
  - Music EXPO. Contact Sheet. 2003 (Box 122)
  - Music EXPO. Consultants. 2003 (Box 122)
  - Music EXPO. Business. 2003 (Box 122)
  - Music EXPO. Budget. 2003 (Box 122)
  - Music EXPO. Transmittals/Memos/Correspondence. 2003 (Box 122)
  - Music EXPO. Peter. 2003 (Box 122)
  - World Trade Center Memorial. 2003 (Box 122)
  - Airport. 2003 (Box 122)
  - Airport. Contract. 2003 (Box 122)
  - Airport. Transmittals/Memos/Correspondence. 2003 (Box 122)
  - Airport. Graphics Renderings Disc. 2003 (Box 122)
  - Studio. 2003 (Box 122)
  - Studio. Thorton, CO. 2003 (Box 122)
  - Studio. Yale Alumni Magazine Interview. 2003 (Box 122)
  - A Family Affair. 2003 (Box 122)
  - Lincoln Center. 2003 (Box 122)
  - Studio. 2003 (Box 122)
  - Studio. Model Lighting. 2003 (Box 122)
  - Studio. Christmas Card. 2003 (Box 122)